Guide to the Brown Brothers Harriman Records 1696-1973, 1995 (bulk, 1820-1968) MS 78
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Historical Files (1699-1974), 1820-1968; 39 Linear feet (81 document boxes, 6 oversize boxes, 12 volumes)
  - Subseries A. Chronological Files (1796-1970), 1818-1968; 31 document boxes, XX OS boxes, 6 volumes
    - James Brown letters to Howard Potter: original and transcript, 1867 September 25, 1868 February 18 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 10)
    - Various private correspondence: originals and letterpress copies, 1867 (Offsite-box 11, Folder 11)
    - Looking down Wall Street from Trinity: print of stereoscopic photo, c. 1867 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1)
    - Howard Potter, F.A. Hamilton, John Crosby Brown, Clarence Brown correspondence re partnership problems: originals and letterpress copies, 1868 March 3-August 25 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 2)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. letters to Brown Bros. & Co.: originals, 1868 July 2, July 27 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 3)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. (London) private letters to Brown Bros. & Co.: originals and letterpress copies (1/2), 1868 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. (London) private letters to Brown Bros. & Co.: originals and letterpress copies (2/2), 1868 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 5)
    - "Brown Brothers and Pacific Mail" article; background on The Revolution Journal: photocopies, 1868 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 6)
    - Ledger cover with rules governing granting of credit, 1869 Feb 8, 1872 May 23 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 7)
    - "Completion of the Pacific railroad, May 10, 1869"; Union Pacific Railroad Station, Wyoming territory; typographical ornaments: images (Offsite-box 12, Folder 8)
    - Ornamental title page, Great Trans-Continental P.R.R. Tourists' Guide; Liverpool docks; envelope sent by balloon post; Bartlett & Greene's warehouses, Brooklyn: images, 1870-1871 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 9)
    - Private correspondence from Boston and Philadelphia offices: originals and letterpress copies, 1870-1872 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 10)
    - Background research, 1870-1873, 1878 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 11)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1870-1875 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 12)
    - Advertisement for "Belt of Life": Col. John Smith Preston; John Crosby Brown: images, 1870s (Offsite-box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence John Crosby Brown, Herman Hoskier, Stewart Henry Brown, Howard Potter, Alexander Hargreaves Brown: originals and letterpress copies, 1871 February 17-1873 November 1 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 14)
    - "P.T. Barnum's Great Traveling World's Fair"; Central elevators, Chicago; California Street, San Francisco; Chicago showing new buildings; Lewis Tappan: images, 1873 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 15)
    - Residence of W. C. Ralston, Belmont, CA; Tick House restaurant, California; Grand Hotel, California; "Jay Cooke & Co.'s office"; "Tompkins Square...": images, 1873 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cotton train in Texas: image, 1873-1874 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 17)
    - Supreme Court judgment: Stewart Brown and trustees of Sarah Benedict Brown vs. James Brown, Sarah Benedict Brown, and others, 1874 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 18)
    - Phosphate works near Charleston, S.C.; Canal Street, New Orleans; Charleston House, Charleston, S.C.; "A Saturday afternoon in a Southampton town": images, 1874 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
    - "A cotton-steamer"; "A cotton wagon-train": images, 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
    - Background research, 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1874-1875 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    - Robert Lenox Kennedy; loading cotton on shipboard at Savannah levee; cotton bales descending a chute; Up-country cotton press, Georgia: images, 1875 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 5)
    - Statements of account: American and English partners: letterpress copies, 1876 October 31, November 14 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 6)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. correspondence: originals and letterpress copies, 1877-1878 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 7)
    - "The cotton exchange"; Loading and unloading Pier 6, East River; invitation to 25th anniversary, Atlantic Telegraph Co.: images, 1877-1879 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 8)
    - Boston office notice: George E. Bullard and Louis Curtis taking over business of Daniel Sargent Curtis, 1878 January 1 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 9)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. telephone listings, 1878-1880s (Offsite-box 13, Folder 10)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. correspondence: originals and letterpress copies, 1880 October 22-1881 January 6 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 11)
    - Letters and cables re problems arising from James Brown's will: originals and letterpress copies, 1880 December 20-1881 February 16 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 12)
    - Certificate for continued use of name; co-partnership advertisement, 1880 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 13)
    - Wall Street west from below Hanover Street; James Muncaster Brown; Donegall Place, Belfast; White Linen Hall, Belfast: images, 1880-1881 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 14)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1880-1884 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 15)
    - Herman Hoskier retirement: original letter, 1881 January 13-1882 March 13 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 16)
    - James M. Brown guarantee of Wright Co. losses; participation in J.P. Morgan syndicate; correspondence re partnership articles; other Brown Bros. & Co. matters: originals and letterpress copies, 1881 February-April (Offsite-box 13, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence re partnership matters: originals and letterpress copies, 1881 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 18)
    - Background research, 1881-1883 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence re partnership agreement; partners' wills, hiring decisions: originals and letterpress copies, 1882 April 1; 1883 April 29, May 31 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 20)
    - Anton Bruckner; invitation to Brooklyn Bridge opening; invitation to Washington statue unveiling, Treasury Building, Wall Street: images, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 21)
    - East River, front view; John Crosby Brown; Brown Bros. & Co. building, 59 Wall Street; "Christmas Carnival in the New York Stock Exchange"; Pasque Island Fishing Club members: images, 1884-1886 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 22)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1884-1886 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 23)
    - Background research, 1884-1886 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence of Howard Potter, F.G. Hamilton, Fred Chalmers, James M. Brown re Liverpool office: originals and letterpress copies, 1885 June 20-November 19 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 25)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. and Brown Bros. & Co. correspondence re Gilbert de S. Hamilton resignation, power of attorney, etc.: originals and letterpress copies, 1885 July 14-August 17 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re C.D. Dickey, Thomasson power of attorney, interest reduction, etc.: originals and letterpress copies, 1885 August 29-1889 January 4 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    - Financing for Mold & Denbigh Railroad, Shrewsbury & Potteries Railroad: originals and photocopies, 1886 November (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
    - John Crosby Brown letters and telegrams: originals, photocopies, letterpress copies, 1887 July, August; 1888 March 22 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
    - Second of exchange to order of William S. Wilkinson: original, 1887 August 3 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1887-1889 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
    - E.H. Harriman with railroad men, Rockford, IL; Chesapeake & Ohio Railroad tour of inspection; Rock Island Railroad tour of inspection; George Washington statue during blizzard: images, 1887-1888 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    - Clippings on decisions favoring Brown Bros. & Co. in Banque Franco-Egyptienne case, 1888 March 23 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 8)
    - Endorsed travelers check, 1888 May 26 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 9)
    - Syndicate histories: bond issues from Philadelphia and other offices, 1888-1889 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 10)
    - John Crosby Brown letters to daughter Amy Brighthurst Brown (DeForest): typed transcripts, 1888 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 11)
    - Background research, 1889 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 12)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1889-1893 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 13)
    - John Crosby Brown letter book and press copies, 1891-1902 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 14)
    - Howard Potter/ Charles D. Dickey correspondence re supplemental arrangements: originals, 1892 October 11 - December 9 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 15)
    - Powers of attorney to Brown Bros. & Co. New York (Lawrence H. Mills, Eng.), London (James F. Pierce), 1892 November 16; 1893 January 25 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 16)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Howard Potter; "Golden Door" entrance to Transportation Building, Chicago World's Fair; James Muncaster Brown: images, 1893 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 17)
    - First typed partners' letter: cipher for partner names, 1894 March 12 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 18)
    - Powers of attorney: Emma Florence Holland, George W. Holland, Carrie Leacock, 1894 July 26; 1895 November 6 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence on partnership matters and new articles: originals and letterpress copies, 1894 December 12-1895 September 5 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 20)
    - "The Webb Academy and Home for Ship-Builders"; "Dr. Parkhurst Receiving Callers in his Parlor"; Brooklyn Bridge and East River from tower of Produce Exchange; "John Pierpont Morgan"; Steamship Row above Bowling Green, NY: images, 1894-1895 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 21)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1894-1896 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 22)
    - John Crosby Brown and others visit Niagara Power Plant; John Crosby Brown and other Columbia University trustees: images, 1895 August; 1896 May 2 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    - John W. Foster/ John Crosby Brown letters: copies from Yale University Library, 1895 December (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    - Background research, 1895 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence on effects of Howard Potter and Charles D. Dickey deaths; other business matters: originals, 1897 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1897-1899 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    - Background research, 1898 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - "The Bread Line"; New York Stock Exchange telephone booths; article "Brown in Town": images, 1898 - 1899 March 9 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - Power of attorney: Cornelia Fuller Devens, 1899 December 9 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence on partnership matters: originals, 1899-1900 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
    - Background research, 1890s (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
    - Wall Street looking towards Trinity from South Street; "Old Boys Club," Mohonk Lake, NY; John Crosby Brown; four generations of Baltimore Browns: images, 1890s (Offsite-box 15, Folder 11)
    - Brown family correspondence: originals and photocopies, 1900 November 19-23; 1903, 1906 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 13)
    - Powers of attorney: William A. Bull re Wisconsin Central Railroad Company; Frederick B. Miles; Baring, Magoun & Co. and Brown Bros. & Co. to Vivanti Brothers, Yokohama, Japan; Sarah B. Turner, 1900 May 4, May 11; 1902 March, December (Offsite-box 15, Folder 12)
    - John Crosby Brown and three sons; postcard sent to Moses Paniente; appeal for contributions to India famine relief: images, 1900 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 14)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1900-1904 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 16)
    - Background research, 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 15)
    - "A Conference of America's Greatest Railroad Magnates"; "J. Pierpont Morgan, Jr."; Alexander Brown with family; Brown Bros. & Co. advertisements, Harper's Weekly; Howard Potter portrait; interior of railroad sleeping car: images, 1901-1903 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 17)
    - Supreme Court summons: John Crosby Brown and James Crosby Brown vs. Sir William Richmond Brown, Bart., and others, 1903 January 12 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 18)
    - Notice of partnership changes, 1904 January 1 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 19)
    - Commercial credits, commissions, and recoveries, 1904-1911 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 20)
    - Advertisement for "The Overland Limited"; Davies cartoon about Harriman; Eugene Delano; advertisement: "Giving St. Nicholas a lift with an Oldsmobile": originals, 1905 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 21)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1905-1907 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 22)
    - Background research, 1905-1907 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 23)
    - Thatcher Brown family correspondence: transcripts, 1906 January 5-September 14 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 24)
    - Bills for work done at Harriman estate, 1906 January 29 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 25)
    - "Extract report of Mr. James Brown's European trip in the fall of 1906", 1906 autumn (Offsite-box 15, Folder 26)
    - James Brown correspondence re establishing a representative in Paris: originals and carbons, 1906 December 29-1907 April 26 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 27)
    - Sir Alexander Hargreaves Brown and family; E.H. Harriman in Texas; Brooklyn Bridge elevated train terminus; Wall Street at night; cartoon: "Mr. Harriman's plan for reorganizing the railways of the country": images, 1906-1908 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 28)
    - Thatcher Brown and Moreau Delano partnerships: images, 1907 January 1 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence re financial plan of 1907, 1907 May 8-1910 January 18 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence re bank committees, New York, Boston, Philadelphia, 1907 May 22-June 7 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    - Cables re Blue Bills, 1907 May (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re Panic of 1907, 1907 August-November (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    - Power of attorney by Brown Bros. & Co. to George L. Diehl (Buffalo agency), 1907 October 30 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - Thatcher Brown letters re Panic of 1907: transcripts (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum re reorganization and resumption of Knickerbocker Trust Co., 1907-1908 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    - Thatcher M. Brown/ John Crosby Brown correspondence: transcripts, 1908 April - June (Offsite-box 16, Folder 9)
    - Thatcher M. Brown letters to his mother from European trip: transcripts, 1908 Spring (Offsite-box 16, Folder 10)
    - Powers of attorney: Winifred Benson Marsh, Jacob Terkwile, 1908 June 19, July 8 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 11)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. cricket club annual dinner program; Bank of England and Royal Exchange: images, 1908 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 12)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1908-1910 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 13)
    - Papers Relating to the Foreign Relations of the United States: photocopies, 1909, 1912-1914, 1916, 1917 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 14)
    - The Nation, May 31, June 7, 1922-Nicaragua: photocopy, 1910-1913 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 15)
    - Fiscal Intervention in Nicaragua, 1933: photocopy, 1910-1920 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 16)
    - Summaries of information on and approaches to Nicaragua episode, 1911-1912 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 17)
    - Excerpts, diary of James Brown 1910-1917: transcript and annotations, 1911-1917 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 18)
    - Dollars for Bullets, 1929: photocopies, 1911-1920 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 19)
    - Memorandum of H.A. Caley, Manager, National Bank of Nicaragua: typescript, 1911-1924 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 20)
    - The Outlook, January 3, 1914, February 22, 1928: photocopies, 1911-1924 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 21)
    - Everybody's Magazine, June 1916; "Dollar Diplomacy at Work in Nicaragua and Mexico": Sen. Burton K. Wheeler speech, March 6, 1927; Nicaragua and the United States, 1909-1927; The Shark and the Sardines, 1961: photocopies, 1911-1924 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 22)
    - Cross reference sheets [Nicaragua], 1911-1927 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 23)
    - American Foreign Investments, 1926; Hearings Before the Subcommittee of the Committee on Foreign Relations, 1927: photocopies, 1911-1927 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 24)
    - Linton Wells memorandum on Brown Bros. & Co. and J.W. Seligman involvement in Nicaraguan affairs: photocopies, 1911-1929 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 25)
    - The World's Work, June and July 1912-Nicaragua: photocopies, 1912 June, July (Offsite-box 16, Folder 26)
    - Excerpt: Confidential Hearings, Committee on Foreign Relations U.S. Senate: Nicaragua, 1912 October (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - Head office, National Bank of Nicaragua; 'Soldiers protecting the special Train at Managua, Nicaragua'; General Chamorro in streets of Managua, Nicaragua; Bank of Nicaragua draft; soldiers putting gun on Sec'y Knox's train: images, 1912 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - North American Review: Vol. 196, re Nicaragua: photocopy, 1912 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - Excerpt from Thatcher M. Brown scrapbook, 1908-1915, 1912 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - Statement showing recovery for Nicaragua loan, 1912-1913 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bankers' letter to President of Nicaragua, 1924, 1912-1924 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Commercial and Financial Chronicle, July 15, 1915; The American Review of Reviews, Feb. 1916; The Five Republics of Central America, 1918; Central American currency and finance, 1925; Dollar Diplomacy, 1925: photocopies, 1912-1925 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - Steam railroad, Nicaragua: image, c. 1912 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - Confidential hearings: Committee on Foreign Relations, U.S. Senate: Nicaragua-transcript, 1914 June (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - Commercial credits, drafts drawn under, commissions, 1909-1913 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1910-1914 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 11)
    - Background research, 1910-1914 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence re partnership issues, credit position, committee system; death of James May Duane, 1912 April-December 4 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 13)
    - Postcard views of New York City; Brown Bros. & Co. signature card (original); house of Marcus Wallenberg, Stockholm: photo, 1912, 1913 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Charles Dickey, Eugene Delano, and others, 1913 July-September 27 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 15)
    - Background research (Gold Fund of 1914) (Offsite-box 17, Folder 16)
    - Power of attorney to W. Gerard Vermilye; analysis of assets and liabilities; partnership correspondence, 1914 April, June (Offsite-box 17, Folder 17)
    - Gold Fund of 1914: cables-originals and transcripts, 1914 July - August (Offsite-box 17, Folder 18)
    - Gold Pool of 1914: cables-Joseph Brown, M. Norman, Brown Shipley & Co., Brown Bros. & Co., 1914 July - October (Offsite-box 17, Folder 19)
    - Gold Fund committee meeting minutes, 1914 August (Offsite-box 17, Folder 20)
    - Gold Fund of 1914: telegrams and letter-transcripts, 1914 August (Offsite-box 17, Folder 21)
    - Gold Pool of 1914: Committee on Foreign Exchange, 1914 August-September (Offsite-box 17, Folder 22)
    - Gold Pool of 1914: Bankers' conference, October 23, 1914, 1914 August-November (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - Gold Pool of 1914: Anglo-American conference, 1914 November-1915 January (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    - Background research (Gold Pool of 1914) (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    - Cross-reference sheet (Gold Fund of 1914), 1914-1919 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    - James Brown correspondence, 1915 January 8-1917 February (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - Gold Pool of 1914: correspondence James Brown, Benjamin Strong, 1915 February-1917 December (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. correspondence, 1915 May 25-1916 December 6 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Atlantic Fleet, May 16, 1915; Eugene Delano; Leonard W. Jerome; Lord Cunliffe and Lloyd George; New York v. Philadelphia Brown Bros. & Co. office baseball game: images (Offsite-box 18, Folder 8)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1915 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 9)
    - Powers of attorney, 1916 January 20-1917 October 1917 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 10)
    - Article on real estate at Hanover and Beaver Sts.; Brown Brothers: images, 1916, 1917 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 11)
    - Thatcher M. Brown, James Brown correspondence, 1917 January 18, April (Offsite-box 18, Folder 12)
    - Clippings from Thatcher M. Brown scrapbook, 1916-1927: photocopies, 1917 February, June (Offsite-box 18, Folder 13)
    - Clippings: James Crosby Brown trip to France, 1917 August (Offsite-box 18, Folder 14)
    - 59 Wall Street building: article, images, 1917 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 15)
    - Partnership agreements, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 16)
    - Johnson/ Beers/ Robinson opinions on American tax questions, 1914 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, side agreements, memoranda, legal arguments: of Brown Shipley & Co. and Brown Bros. & Co., 1915 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Formula for closing books at end of year, 1915-1917 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - Partners agreement: U.S. and European business, 1915-1917 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - Partial separation, Brown Shipley & Co. and Brown Bros. & Co., 1915-1917 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence re partnership, 1917 April-November (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - Cables between London and New York about partnership agreement, 1917-1918 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - List of banks of deposit, 1918 January - 1939 November (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - Powers of attorney by Brown Bros. & Co. to partners, 1918 April 29-1919 July 16 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    - James Brown correspondence, 1918 April-1919 September (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - Brown Shipley & Co. advertisements; Brown and Blewett aboard Oscar II; invitation to T. Brown from Marcus Wallenberg; letter T.M. Brown to Caro Noyes Brown from Grand Hotel; letter sent by dirigible: images, 1918 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)
    - Cross reference sheets, 1918-1919 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 11)
    - Partners' account, New York, 1918 December 31 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 12)
    - James Crosby Brown letter to wife Agnes Hewlett Brown, 1919 October 8 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 13)
    - American Foreign Investments, 1926: photocopy, 1919 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 14)
    - Powers of attorney, 1920 January 19- 1922 November 29 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 15)
    - James Brown correspondence, 1920 January - December (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1)
    - 59 Wall Street: booklet and photos, 1920 December (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Commercial credit department, 59 Wall Street; James Brown private office; Wall Street explosion; Wallenberg letter re Nobel Prize: images, 1920 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Background research, 1920-1922 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1920-1922 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Moreau Delano; ABC of Bankers Acceptances (title page): images, c. 1920 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. newspaper advertisements, 1921 February-1923 December (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - Announcement of George Frazier retirement, 1921 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda on pensions and bonuses, 1921-1929 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)
    - W.A. Harriman: photo, 1922 October (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - Powers of attorney, 1923 January 2-1925 January 23 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - Brown Bros. & Co. booklet: "A Study of the Louisville & Nashville Railroad Company": photocopy and images, 1923 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 12)
    - Cross-reference sheets, 1923-1925 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 13)
    - James Brown correspondence: originals, 1924 November-1925 October (Offsite-box 20, Folder 14)
    - R. A. Lovett report on distribution of expenses and analysis of deposit accounts, 1924 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 15)
    - 100th anniversary dinner: invitations, menu, 1925 December 18 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 16)
    - 100th anniversary dinner: attendees, 1925 December 18 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 17)
    - 100th anniversary dinner: speeches, 1925 December 18 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 18)
    - 100th anniversary dinner: expenses, entertainment, commemorative clock and booklet, 1925 December 18 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 19)